I know zero Japanese. I need one table for one.
MA starts with one useful phrase, not an empty conversation.
The support disappears: full phrase, rhythm, then no answer text.
I decide whether I completed it. MA does not pretend to grade pronunciation.
Now the bundled restaurant scene sounds natural—and quickly becomes noise.
I tap Pause and help. MA stops its local tutor audio on that explicit tap.
This is one complete controlled segment, not an exact replay of what I heard.
MA turns that segment into a tiny Spanish repair lesson.
Then I return to the same obligation: a restaurant table for one.
I try again without answer text and self-assess a fresh attempt.
The proof compares bounded facts, not a score or a claim of mastery.
The next step works locally. I can explicitly opt in to a GPT-5.6 recommendation.
Only structured attempt facts leave the phone—never audio or a transcript.
I built the teacher I needed for when real Japanese becomes noise.